{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following functions can a cognitive AI system perform?",
      "correct_answers": ["Interact", "Learn", "Understand", "Reason"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the final step an AI debater system must take?",
      "correct_answers": ["Respond to the opponent by listening to the opponent's arguments to then deliver a convincing rebuttal that refutes the opponent and further proves the case."]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is correct about natural language processing (NLP)?",
      "correct_answers": [
        "IBM Project Debater was a major step forward in the field of natural language processing.",
        "Human language is complex, so machines require natural language processing systems to understand human language."
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank. A system that helps machines understand cultural knowledge, grammatical structures, and various language nuances is known as _____________________.",
      "correct_answers": ["natural language processing"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What term do AI researchers use to describe the collection of text and data they use to train a debater AI system?",
      "correct_answers": ["Corpus"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Your friend says, “I really love anchovies and flowers.” How many relationships between entities can you find in this statement?",
      "correct_answers": ["Two"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is sentiment analysis?",
      "correct_answers": ["A method to measure the strength of an emotion by assessing data as positive, negative, or neutral"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of problem does the following sentence create for an AI system?",
      "correct_answers": ["Classification problem"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How does an AI system that is working with human language handle the classification problem?",
      "correct_answers": ["It learns from many instances."]
    },
    {
      "question": "You’re consulting for a store that wants to know how customers feel about a new product line. You propose an AI system that can study how people feel about these products based on their comments in social media.",
      "correct_answers": ["Emotions and sentiment"]
    },
    {
      "question": "For a chatbot, what is an entity considered within the context of a question?",
      "correct_answers": ["A node"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is true about industries in which AI professionals work?",
      "correct_answers": ["Most industries have already hired or are in the process of hiring AI professionals."]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary job role of a business intelligence developer?",
      "correct_answers": ["To analyze complex data, looking at business and market trends to increase profitability of their organization"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which AI professional specializes in human language and works on voice assistants and speech recognition?",
      "correct_answers": ["Natural language processing engineer"]
    },
    {
      "question": "You’re in a job interview and you are asked to describe your advanced AI technical skills. What set of skills should you elaborate on?",
      "correct_answers": ["Python, TensorFlow, and machine learning"]
    },
    {
      "question": "You’re applying for an entry-level job as an AI professional. The interviewer asks you about your workplace skills. Which of the following skills should you elaborate on?",
      "correct_answers": ["Communication and teamwork"]
    },
    {
      "question": "When developing explanations for the output of an AI model, it is important to remember that explanations must ___________ depending on the user persona.",
      "correct_answers": ["vary"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of poisoning in the AI context?",
      "correct_answers": [
        "Updating features and labels of the training data",
        "Injecting malicious samples into the training data",
        "Corrupting test data sent to the deployed model"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank. A distinguishing feature of generative AI, as opposed to other types of AI, is its ability to ___________.",
      "correct_answers": ["create new content"]
    },
    {
      "question": "When you selected the CSV file in All assets, what did you see?",
      "correct_answers": ["A preview of the data to be used when training your model"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes how information flows through the nodes of a perceptron in a neural network?",
      "correct_answers": ["Information flows from the input layer to the hidden layers, where algorithms are applied, and then to the output layer."]
    },
    {
      "question": "What term do AI researchers use to describe the collection of text and data they use to train a debater AI system?",
      "correct_answers": ["Corpus"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following pillars of AI is exemplified by anyone being able to describe how an AI system makes a prediction or recommendation?",
      "correct_answers": ["Explainability"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following business roles is responsible for the deployment of AI models?",
      "correct_answers": ["AI Ops Engineer"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In a poisoning attack, when does the adversarial attack occur?",
      "correct_answers": ["Training phase"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes a robust AI system?",
      "correct_answers": ["The AI system can effectively handle malicious attacks without causing unintentional harm."]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a limitation of generative AI?",
      "correct_answers": [
        "Lack of originality in content",
        "Bias in the generated content",
        "Accuracy of content"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is sentiment analysis?",
      "correct_answers": ["A method to measure the strength of an emotion by assessing data as positive, negative, or neutral"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes an AI system, that everyday people, who do not have any special training in AI, can understand how and why the system came to a particular prediction or recommendation?",
      "correct_answers": ["Understandable"]
    },
    {
            "question": "Which of the following functions can a cognitive AI system perform?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Interact",
                "Learn",
                "Understand",
                "Reason"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the final step an AI debater system must take?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Build the final position by creating a final speech that details the position on the debate topic and gives a compelling argument."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following statements is correct about natural language processing (NLP)?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "IBM Project Debater was a major step forward in the field of natural language processing.",
                "Human language is complex, so machines require natural language processing systems to understand human language."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank. A system that helps machines understand cultural knowledge, grammatical structures, and various language nuances is known as _____________________.",
            "correct_answers": [
                "natural language processing"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What term do AI researchers use to describe the collection of text and data they use to train a debater AI system?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Corpus"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Your friend says, \u201cI really love anchovies and flowers.\u201d How many relationships between entities can you find in this statement?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Two"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is sentiment analysis?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "A method to measure the strength of an emotion by assessing data as positive, negative, or neutral"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of problem does the following sentence create for an AI system? 'Is your refrigerator running?'",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Token movement problem"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How does an AI system that is working with human language handle the classification problem?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "It learns from many instances."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "You\u2019re consulting for a store that wants to know how customers feel about a new product line. You propose an AI system that can study how people feel about these products based on their comments in social media. What should the AI analyze?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Emotions and sentiment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "For a chatbot, what is an entity considered within the context of a question?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "A noun"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following terms is used to describe the reason why a user sends a message in a chatbot?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Intent"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following describes how chatbots differ from more general AI systems in their capabilities?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Chatbots are focused on answering specific questions in a limited domain."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following processes is used by AI to analyze only small parts of an image at a time, making it possible for visual recognition systems to identify parts of an image?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Convolutional neural network (CNN)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following methods of learning describes how an AI system learns using trial and error?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Reinforcement learning"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which level of AI refers to machines that can perform any intellectual task that a human can?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "General AI"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of algorithm would help you \ufb01nd out what you might earn for a salary if you have different levels of college degrees in computer science?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Linear regression"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "You want to know how many hours to study to pass an exam. The \u201chours of studying\u201d data forms a sigmoid function, or an S-shaped curve, between \u201cfail\u201d and \u201cpass\u201d. Which learning algorithm could you use?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Logistic regression"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of brain cells inspired the creation of neural networks?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Neurons"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "After calculating values, what do neural networks often assign to those values that impact the final result?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Weight"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which process makes facial recognition possible?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Convolutional neural network (CNN)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is an important difference between linear and logistic regressions?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Only logistic regressions have outputs between 0 and 1."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following terms is used to describe the collection of text and data AI researchers use to train a debater AI system?",
            "correct_answers": [
                "Corpus"
            ]
        },
        {
      "question": "Which of the following is true about industries in which AI professionals work?",
      "correct_answers": ["Most industries have already hired or are in the process of hiring AI professionals."]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary job role of a business intelligence developer?",
      "correct_answers": ["To analyze complex data, looking at business and market trends to increase profitability of their organization"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which AI professional specializes in human language and works on voice assistants and speech recognition?",
      "correct_answers": ["Natural language processing engineer"]
    },
    {
      "question": "You’re in a job interview and you are asked to describe your advanced AI technical skills. What set of skills should you elaborate on?",
      "correct_answers": ["Python, TensorFlow, and machine learning"]
    },
    {
      "question": "You’re applying for an entry-level job as an AI professional. The interviewer asks you about your workplace skills. Which of the following skills should you elaborate on?",
      "correct_answers": ["Communication and teamwork"]
    },
    {
      "question": "When developing explanations for the output of an AI model, it is important to remember that explanations must _______________ depending on the user persona.",
      "correct_answers": ["vary"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an example of poisoning in the AI context?",
      "correct_answers": [
        "Updating features and labels of the training data",
        "Injecting malicious samples into the training data",
        "Corrupting test data sent to the deployed model"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank. A distinguishing feature of generative AI, as opposed to other types of AI, is its ability to _______________.",
      "correct_answers": ["create new content"]
    },
    {
      "question": "When you selected the CSV file in All assets, what did you see?",
      "correct_answers": ["A preview of the data to be used when training your model"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes how information flows through the nodes of a perceptron in a neural network?",
      "correct_answers": ["Information flows from the input layer to the hidden layers, where algorithms are applied, and then to the output layer."]
    },
    {
      "question": "What term do AI researchers use to describe the collection of text and data they use to train a debater AI system?",
      "correct_answers": ["Corpus"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following pillars of AI is exemplified by anyone being able to describe how an AI system makes a prediction or recommendation?",
      "correct_answers": ["Explainability"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following business roles is responsible for the deployment of AI models?",
      "correct_answers": ["AI Ops Engineer"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In a poisoning attack, when does the adversarial attack occur?",
      "correct_answers": ["Training phase"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes a robust AI system?",
      "correct_answers": ["The AI system can effectively handle malicious attacks without causing unintentional harm."]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a limitation of generative AI?",
      "correct_answers": [
        "Lack of originality in content",
        "Bias in the generated content",
        "Accuracy of content"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is sentiment analysis?",
      "correct_answers": ["A method to measure the strength of an emotion by assessing data as positive, negative, or neutral"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes an AI system, that everyday people, who do not have any special training in AI, can understand how and why the system came to a particular prediction or recommendation?",
      "correct_answers": ["Understandable"]
    }
      ]
    }
